{
    "subject": "resource/Hassan_Dandach",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Lebanon",
    "human_readable": "Hassan Dandach was born in Lebanon.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8782172203063965,
            "question": "Where was Hassan Dandach born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8118007779121399,
            "question": "In what year was Hassan Dandach born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4262970983982086,
            "question": "What is Hassan Dandach known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33333832025527954,
            "question": "Has Hassan Dandach traveled to other countries?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31154173612594604,
            "question": "Does Hassan Dandach have any siblings?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2900508940219879,
            "question": "What is Hassan Dandach's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2717421054840088,
            "question": "Does Hassan Dandach have any children?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22789180278778076,
            "question": "What country's citizenship does Hassan Dandach hold?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18789903819561005,
            "question": "Is Hassan Dandach married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1279270350933075,
            "question": "What language does Hassan Dandach speak?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Hassan Dandach was born in Lebanon.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8940_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Hassan Dandach married?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8940_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What country's citizenship does Hassan Dandach hold?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8940_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Hassan Dandach have any children?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8940_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8940_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8940_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8940_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8940_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8940_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8940_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8940_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8940_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8940_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8940_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the provided context information, I can confirm that:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`\n\nThe documents contain multiple mentions of Hassan Dandach's birthplace as Beirut, Beyrouth, or simply Beirut, which is part of Lebanon. This information supports the triple \"Hassan Dandach was born in Lebanon.\""
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that confirms Hassan Dandach was born in Beirut, Lebanon. Specifically, the document states: \"Hassan Dandach was born on May 11, 1991, in Beirut, Beyrouth, Lebanon.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}